

# CONTACT



5 Cyril Ibeto Crescent, Ikenegbu Extension, Owerri, 460242



+2347034605700



annie.ezc@gmail.com

# **SKILLS (TECH STACK)**

- Web Developer: PHP, Laravel, Symfony, Codelgniter, Python, JavaScript, Ajax, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Search Engine Optimization, REST APIs, Vue.js
- Mobile Developer: Cross platform C#, Xamarin Forms
- Databases Microsoft SQL Server 2016, MySQL, SQLite
- Software MS Office Suite, Adobe
   Suite. Visual Studio
- CMS WordPress
- Others GIT, Docker, Vagrant

# EZURIKE, ANNE CHIBUZO

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Highly effective software developer offering a wealth of more than 4 years of expertise. A valuable team player who is also personable and dedicated. Seeking the chance to bring further success to an established organisation through testing, deployment, and software debugging.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

#### **Software Developer**

02/2022 -current

#### Check24 Vergleichsportal Shopping GmbH - Münster

- Further development of growing extranet with PHP7.4 and Symfony.
- Implementation of database queries and migrations with MySQL8
- Conception and implementation of exciting product features together with our IT and product management teams
- Expansion of our automated release process (continous integration), quality assurance (unit testing) and fully automated test systems.

# Instructor – Web Development NIIT Education and Training Center – Owerri

05/2018 - 01/2022

- Utilised various teaching aids to minimise learning gaps and effectively instruct and motivate students.
- Teach frontend and backend technologies HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, MySql, PHP

# PHP Web Developer - PT

02/2017 - 10/2021

### XclusiveA Networks - Owerri, Imo State

- Performed appealing, responsive and user-friendly front and back end web development for range of projects across education, governments, religion and businesses.
- Creation and integration of internal and external APIs using Laravel and Symfony
- Implemented Google campaigns and SEO for various types of websites.
- Employed Laravel and MySQL to meticulously translate client requirements into quality application, maintaining 100% client satisfaction.
- Coordination of development work and tests
- Discuss business requirements

# IT Manager

01/2016 - 01/2017

# Firstlove Assembly - Owerri

- Posted financial data in Excel spreadsheets and managed inventory.
- Wrote clean code to develop fully functional cross platform mobile application.

# Software Programmer Solafrips International - Owerri

- Developed and delivered web application features as defined in product road map
- Worked closely with other business analysts, development teams and infrastructure specialists to deliver high availability solutions for educational institutions.

### **EDUCATION**

HND: Computer Science, 10/2015

Federal Polytechnic Nekede - Owerri, Imo State

**OND**: Software Engineering, 10/2012

NIIT Education and Training Center - Owerri, Imo State

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Google Africa Developer Training Program 2020, Google 2020
- SQL and Relational Databases 101, Big Data University 2019
- Building RESTful APIs in Laravel (2018)
- HND Computer Science, 09/2015
- ND Software Engineering, 08/2012

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Students/Results Management System: Developed using PHP Laravel framework (2019)
- Multimedia Based Virtual Learning System: Developed using PHP Laravel framework (2021)
- Daily Devotional App (Mobile crossplatform): Developed using Xamarin,
   C# (2019, currently on Google Playstore and Windows Appstore)
- Others (websites) https://crimefacts.news, https://delonygroup.com, https://rightbreedacademyowerri.org, https://brainslink.com.ng, https://imodfi.im.gov.ng etc

#### References:

#### • Mr. Offurum Paschal (Lecturer/Employer)

NIIT Education and Training Center, p.offurum@gmail.com 08033126347 Relationship: Mentor/Lecturer/Employer Position: Center Head/Acting Rector

# • Mrs. Chidiebere Opara (Lecturer)

Federal Polytechnic Nekede canonchychuks@yahoo.com 08036183740 Relationship: Lecturer

Position: Senior Lecturer